# **Dylan Albertazzi**

Bend, OR 9702 • (541)678-2132 D.Albertazzi10@gmail.com www.linkedIn.com/in/DAlbertazzi Website: DylanAlbertazzi.com

# **Full Stack - Software Engineer**

Software Development / Cloud Technologies / Business Development

Proven experience using technology to increase the profitability of businesses. Over 7 years of coding experience with a heavy focus on web and cloud technologies. Possess great leadership skills and a team-first mentality. Diverse background in technical and creative work with demonstrated ability in bringing both together to reach the goals and increase revenue for clients.

# **Areas of Expertise:**

#### Software Development, Self-Initiative, Realization of Client Goals, Collaboration

- AWS Solutions Architect Associate Certification
- AWS Developer Associate Certification
- AWS Cloud Practitioner Certification
- Client and Results Oriented
- Effective Verbal and Written Communication skills, including Presentations.

## **Professional Experience**

## Effectual • Bend, OR

Feb. 2021 - present

#### **Cloud Engineer**

Builds full-stack web and mobile applications on AWS for fortune 500 companies, among others. Named an AWS Premier Partner, Effectual uses small, agile teams to build and manage AWS workloads at scale for large companies and government organizations.

## Industry:

• Transportation, Manufacturing

## Albertazzi Law Firm • Bend, OR

Jun. 2018 - present

#### Web Development

Dylan's website and search engine optimization strategy generated new business leads that attracted enough clients to minimize the need for paid referrals, saving the firm an estimated 12% in annual referral expenses. Demonstrated abilities for user interface design, high care for user experience, and partnership in the long-term vision of the firm.

#### Contributions:

- 57% increase in new clients retained from the internet.
- Over \$115,000 in **increased** profits as a direct result of clients obtained from the new website and SEO campaign.

#### Volunteer Experience

# Young Life • Corvallis, OR

Sep. 2016 - Feb. 2018

#### **Organizer and Mentor**

1500+ unpaid hours of volunteer work.

Mentored 12 middle schoolers weekly. Responsible for a team of 10 college leaders, which involved scheduling, training, planning, and conducting weekly meetings. Coordinated with leaders, community, and parents to put on bi-monthly events with the middle schoolers.

## **Skills**

- AWS EC2, Lambda, S3, RDS, VPC, IAM, Amplify, Billing, CloudWatch, Serverless Framework, CI/CD, among others
- JavaScript, Node, React, MongoDB, SQL, Python, C++, GitHub, HTML/CSS
- AWS Management Console, VS Code, Slack, Notion, GSuite, Figma, Office 365, Adobe Creative Suite

## About

Spends free time reading, running, skiing, spending time with family and friends, and creating YouTube videos about technology that enables business.

## **Education**

BS, Mechanical Engineering, Minor Computer Science • Oregon State University – Corvallis, OR

Graduated Mar. 2021, 3.54/4.0 GPA

Honors Diploma • Summit High School – Bend, OR

Graduated Jun. 2016, 3.75/4.0 GPA. Senior Class Representative. 3-time first-team all-conference, baseball.